<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>shan&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on shan&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.128.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:26:40 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://moloxiao.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Six Actionable Steps for Finding a Job</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/six-actionable-steps-for-finding-a-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:26:40 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/six-actionable-steps-for-finding-a-job/</guid>
      <description>Let me introduce six actionable steps for finding a job.
1. get your head right You have to believe that you&amp;rsquo;re going to get a job. Your job is to control what you can control and to shrink the time between now and when you land a job.
2. just do it if you&amp;rsquo;re serious about getting a new job, don&amp;rsquo;t wait to get started. The alternative is wasting years of your life at lower pay with less status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Set Up Google Analytics a Step by Step Guide to Getting Your Measurement Id</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-set-up-google-analytics-a-step-by-step-guide-to-getting-your-measurement-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:03 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-set-up-google-analytics-a-step-by-step-guide-to-getting-your-measurement-id/</guid>
      <description>We use Google Analytics to track the number of visitors to our website, including information about when they visit and how they interact with our site. This helps us understand our audience better and improve our online presence.
when you have a website and want your software engineer to support it with Google Analytics, You need to do two things:
Create a New Property Get the Measurement ID and Send It to Your Software Engineer here is a step-by-step guide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Move Your GoDaddy Domain to Cloudflare a Step by Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-move-your-godaddy-domain-to-cloudflare-a-step-by-step-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:00:29 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-move-your-godaddy-domain-to-cloudflare-a-step-by-step-guide/</guid>
      <description>Managing your domain through Cloudflare offers numerous benefits, including enhanced security, improved website performance, and easy DNS management. These are not the most important factors. The main reason is that you might need my help with day-to-day management, and personally, I prefer Cloudflare.
If you have a domain registered with GoDaddy and want to move it to Cloudflare, follow this detailed step-by-step guide.
Step 1: Create a Cloudflare Account and Add Your Site Create a Cloudflare Account Visit the Cloudflare website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Features in Resume Manager 2</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-features-in-resume-manager-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:46:24 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-features-in-resume-manager-2/</guid>
      <description>Hello, all my friends. Thank you for all your ideas and feedback, help this product better.
We&amp;rsquo;re back! The last update was 18 days ago. This week I use 6 hours to add new feature : Job Application Task Manager. Click here to experience it now.
Here are some of the main interfaces :
New Dashboard Because we added the job application manager, the dashboard has changed.
Job Application List We can add new job applications and change the application status on this page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A First Look At Resume Manager</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/a-first-look-at-resume-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:49:42 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/a-first-look-at-resume-manager/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my friends. Last week, I published a new product: Resume Manager. I have two reasons for creating this product:
to manage my resume and application process, to create a platform for new AI Currently, it is still a demo version, but if you want to try it, you can get started now.
STEP BY STEP visit Resume Manager, click &amp;lsquo;Get Started -&amp;gt;&amp;rsquo; login create new resume change theme Click &amp;lsquo;Next&amp;rsquo; to sequentially edit Personal Detail, Summary, Professional Experience, Education, and Skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating Custom Code Snippets in Vscode</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/creating-custom-code-snippets-in-vscode/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:49:42 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/creating-custom-code-snippets-in-vscode/</guid>
      <description>VSCode provides a powerful snippet feature that helps developers boost their coding efficiency and consistency. This blog will guide you through creating custom code snippets in VSCode, specifically for TypeScript and React projects.
What are Code Snippets? Code snippets are predefined chunks of code that you can quickly insert into your code files using simple shortcuts. They are extremely useful for repetitive tasks or commonly used code templates.
Steps to Manually Create Custom Code Snippets Open VSCode Settings First, open VSCode and press Cmd + Shift + P (Mac) or Ctrl + Shift + P (Windows/Linux) to open the command palette.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minified React Error #130</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/minified-react-error-%23130/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 15:57:51 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/minified-react-error-%23130/</guid>
      <description>When I am unable to find an answer using ChatGPT, Gemini, claude, or Google, I believe it is necessary to document the steps I take to solve the problem.
The problem is :
Unexpected Application Error! Minified React error #130; visit https://reactjs.org/docs/error-decoder.html?invariant=130&amp;amp;args[]=undefined&amp;amp;args[]= for the full message or use the non-minified dev environment for full errors and additional helpful warnings. Error: Minified React error #130; visit https://reactjs.org/docs/error-decoder.html?invariant=130&amp;amp;args[]=undefined&amp;amp;args[]= for the full message or use the non-minified dev environment for full errors and additional helpful warnings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting a blog accepted by Google AdSense</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/getting-a-blog-accepted-by-google-adsense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 10:14:57 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/getting-a-blog-accepted-by-google-adsense/</guid>
      <description>When I first tried to sign up for Google AdSense, I got turned down. Here are the reasons why(the reasons Google gave for turning me down) :
We do not allow Google-served ads on screens: without content or with low value content, that are under construction, that are used for alerts, navigation or other behavioural purposes. So Getting a blog accepted by Google AdSense means you need to creating high quality sites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Yolo to Analyze Youth Football Matches</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/use-yolo-to-analyze-youth-football-matches/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:52:22 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/use-yolo-to-analyze-youth-football-matches/</guid>
      <description>I discuss youth soccer games with my 10-year-old son. I think it&amp;rsquo;s important to first help him understand when making certain decisions is beneficial. So, I&amp;rsquo;m looking for a way to help young athletes develop their decision-making skills.
One important tool for this is watching game videos.
While watching and learning from game videos together, I started thinking about some questions:
Is there a connection between teams that run more and winning?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oduio Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/oduio-roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:37:16 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/oduio-roadmap/</guid>
      <description>last updated on : 2024-07-03
This page displays basic information about the Oduio app,
Oduio means: oh, yes, oh. &amp;lsquo;o&amp;rsquo; stands for &amp;lsquo;oh,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;dui&amp;rsquo; means &amp;lsquo;yes&amp;rsquo; in Chinese pinyin, and &amp;lsquo;o&amp;rsquo; stands for &amp;lsquo;oh.&amp;rsquo;
It is used to express the feeling of a sudden realization. In chinese we say : &amp;lsquo;恍然大悟&amp;rsquo;.
Now Now means plans in progress. Current list :
update news template UI Set the homepage as the LandingPage introduction page, and change the admin dashboard homepage to &amp;lsquo;/home&amp;rsquo; waiting to be scheduled TODO task management module; includes Goal attribute support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 10:57:29 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy
Introduction
Welcome to Shan&amp;rsquo;s Blog. Your privacy is critically important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit our Blog, as well as your rights under GDPR, CPRA, CCPA, CPA, and VCDPA. Please read this policy carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.
Information We Collect
We collect information about you in a variety of ways:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a blog using Hugo</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/create-a-blog-using-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:57:29 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/create-a-blog-using-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Just like you see, this blog you are visiting is created using Hugo and hosted on GitHub Pages. In the process of using Hugo, I researched a lot to answer my questions. Here are some common issues.
How to Create Pages and Posts with Hugo Commands To create a new post in Hugo, you can use the following command:
hugo new posts/your-post-title.md For example, if you want to create a new post titled &amp;ldquo;my-first-post,&amp;rdquo; you would run:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
