<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Shan&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shan&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.128.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:14:29 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://moloxiao.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Preface</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/modern-woodworking/preface/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 10:53:43 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/modern-woodworking/preface/</guid>
      <description>Modern Woodworking
Training Plan for Supporting Scanning Solution in Wood Processing :
Wood Processing Industry Knowledge Technical Skills Development Part 1 : Wood Processing Industry Knowledge Understand the wood processing industry, including common challenges and how the Scanning Solution addresses these :
Overview of the wood processing industry Common processes and workflows in wood processing Challenges faced in wood processing and how the Scanning Solution provides solutions Part 2 : Technical Skills Development Develop technical skills necessary for troubleshooting and supporting the Scanning Solution :</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preface</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/preface/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 10:53:43 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/preface/</guid>
      <description>I wrote this book while preparing for a System Administration job. It serves as a structured summary of my previous work, developed through studying Google&amp;rsquo;s course on &amp;lsquo;System Administration and IT Infrastructure Services&amp;rsquo; and it also functions as a quick-reference guide.
I&amp;#39;m trying to understand what success looks like and how we can achieve it, so that we can repeat those patterns over and over again. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1 : The fundamentals of Coaching</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/youth-sports-coaching/chapter1-the-fundamentals-of-coaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:53:43 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/youth-sports-coaching/chapter1-the-fundamentals-of-coaching/</guid>
      <description>Coach is a misnormer. What you really are is a facilitator and teacher.
As a facilitator: Ensure a good experience for the kids. As a teacher: Teach skills effectively. 1 What is a good experience for the kids TODO
2 The roles in the coaching team 3 Assessing Your Progress I learn this from a book &amp;lsquo;The Confident Coach&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Teaching Youth Soccer&amp;rsquo; By Joe Provey. This is a tutorial for football coaches, but I think it is suitable for any project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is System Administration</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/what-is-system-administration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:30:43 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/what-is-system-administration/</guid>
      <description>The basics of system administration :
organizational policies IT infrastructure services user and hardware provisioning routine maintenance troubleshooting managing potential issues Not contains in this book, like :
automate workflow managed configrations computer settings automatically What is systems administration Servers Revisited Basically, a sys admin is responsible for their company&amp;rsquo;s IT service. Employees need these IT services so that they can be productive.
System Administration Tasks Organizational Policies IT infrastructure User and Hardware Provisioning(Procurement-&amp;gt;Deployment-&amp;gt;Maintenance-&amp;gt;Retirement) Routine Maintenance Vendors Troubleshooting and Managing Issues In Case of Fire, Break Glass(You can&amp;rsquo;t account for everything but you can be prepared to recover from it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network and infrastructure services</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/networking-and-infrastructure-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:30:43 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/networking-and-infrastructure-services/</guid>
      <description>We will cover what IT infrastructure services are and what their role is in system administration. We&amp;rsquo;ll also learn about server operating systems, virtualization, network services, DNS for web services, and how to troubleshoot network services.
Physical infrastructure services Server Operating System Virtuallization(There are two ways you can run your services, either on dedicated hardware or on a virtualized instance on a server) Remote Access(the ability to connect to your infrastructure from anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software and Platform Services</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/software-and-platform-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 14:17:43 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/software-and-platform-services/</guid>
      <description>Software services are the services that employs use that allow them to do their daily job functions. This can include applications like Word processors, Internet browsers, email clients, chat clients, and so on.
Software Service Communication Services :
The 5 best team chat apps for the workplace :
Slack for a chat-powered workplace Microsoft Teams for large organizations broken down into teams Google Chat for Google Workspace users Discord for always-on voice chat Element for self-hosted team chat Open IM chat applications click here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directory Service</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/directory-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 16:40:12 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/directory-service/</guid>
      <description>we&amp;rsquo;ll cover how two of the most popular directory services, Active Directory and OpenLDAP, work in action. We&amp;rsquo;ll explore the concept of centralized management and how this can help SysAdmins maintain and support all the different parts of an IT infrastructure.
Introduction to Directory Services What is a Directory Service?
It&amp;rsquo;s akin to a phone directory for a network, mapping resources like user accounts and network shares to their network addresses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Recovery and Backups</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/data-recovery-and-backups/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 09:30:12 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/data-recovery-and-backups/</guid>
      <description>we&amp;rsquo;re going to arm you with tools you need to be prepared for these accidents, so you can minimize the impact and loss of data.
Data recovery, in general terms, is the process of trying to restore data after an unexpected event that results in data loss or corruption.
Planning for Data Recovery Backing Up Your Data : you should only be backing up data that&amp;rsquo;s absolutely necessary for operations and can be found in another source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>System Administration Consultation</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/system-administration-consultation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 19:12:12 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/system-administration-and-it-infrastructure-services/system-administration-consultation/</guid>
      <description>Scenario 1 You’re doing systems administration work for Network Funtime Company. Evaluate their current IT infrastructure needs and limitations, then provide at least five process improvements and rationale behind those improvements. Write a 200-400 word process review for this consultation. Remember, there’s no right or wrong answer, but make sure to provide your reasoning.
Software Company :
Network Funtime Company is a small company that builds open-source software. The company is made up software engineers, a few designers, one person in Human Resources (HR), and a small sales team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common Woodworking Products</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/modern-woodworking/common-woodworking-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 17:22:43 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/modern-woodworking/common-woodworking-products/</guid>
      <description>Modern Woodworking
Cladding interior products sawmill wood fuels truss &amp;amp; frame </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USNR Scanning Solution</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/modern-woodworking/usnr-scanning-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 10:21:03 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/books/modern-woodworking/usnr-scanning-solution/</guid>
      <description>Modern Woodworking
What is our goal When we start doing something, we aim to :
do the right things do things right We believe currently we do the right things, but We need continuously enhance processes by staying informed about the latest technological advancements and improvements, and advising on the replacement of outdated technologies or software.
optimize wood recovery reduce waste Analyze data :
identify improvement areas Conduct production simulations to evaluate performance and pinpoint strategic opportunities for optimization and enhancement Train :</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customize Your Resume According to the Job Description</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/customize-your-resume-according-to-the-job-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:14:29 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/customize-your-resume-according-to-the-job-description/</guid>
      <description>In the current Resume Manager application, the module I use the most on a daily basis is the job application module, with its core feature being the tracking of resume submissions. Moving forward, I want to enhance the ability to match resumes with job requirements. This will involve the following steps:
Analysis of the recruitment process and the needs of each stage Resume Match evaluation Process adjustment 1 Analysis of the recruitment process and the needs of each stage Stage Goal Evaluation Criteria Resume Screening Initial screening to find candidates that meet basic job requirements Core skills Years of experience Education requirements Career objectives and cultural fit Initial/Phone Interview Further assess communication skills, motivation, and cultural fit Communication skills Career motivation Problem-solving ability Cultural fit Technical Assessment Evaluate candidates&amp;rsquo; technical proficiency and problem-solving skills Technical skills Problem-solving ability Project experience and technical expertise Behavioral/Deep Interview Assess leadership, teamwork, and deeper cultural fit Leadership Teamwork Cultural fit Handling challenges Final Interview/Decision Ensure long-term potential within the company and alignment of compensation expectations Overall competence Role expectations and company growth alignment Salary negotiation and benefits expectations 2 Resume Match evaluation the three most important aspects of a resume are :</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create an Industrial Automation Solutions Website</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/create-an-industrial-automation-solutions-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:43:08 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/create-an-industrial-automation-solutions-website/</guid>
      <description>I want to consolidate my experience and knowledge in the field of automation, and I’ve decided to do this by creating a website. I also hope it can serve as a starting point for offering consulting services.
Since this website is content-focused, I chose to build it using Docusaurus and deployed it on Cloudflare. I spent an hour setting up the template and configuring automated deployment. You can now access it by clicking here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Method for Quickly Mastering the USNR Scanning System</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/a-method-for-quickly-mastering-the-usnr-scanning-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 22:17:29 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/a-method-for-quickly-mastering-the-usnr-scanning-system/</guid>
      <description>I have never used the USNR Scanning system before. This article outlines my plan for quickly mastering the system and developing the capability for ongoing maintenance and improvement.
1 Goals &amp;amp; Metrics The goal can be divided into two stages :
Proficiency : Become familiar with the USNR system as an assistant, understand the manual, learn the operating procedures, and handle common issues. Control : Understand the wood processing steps, and master the role of the USNR system at each step Tasks for Proficiency :</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare for Data Jobs</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-prepare-for-data-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 20:45:47 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-prepare-for-data-jobs/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for data jobs means writing a good resume and passing the job interview.
I want to take immediate action, so I&amp;rsquo;ve set the following principles:
Time allocation principle: Focus on securing interview opportunities before receiving any interviews; once an interview is secured, focus on interview preparation. Take action first, then reflect and improve as you go. Therefore, we start with the resume, which includes two important factors:
A well-formatted resume.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Jobs in 2024</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/data-jobs-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 11:43:19 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/data-jobs-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>1 About Data Jobs Data Jobs(like data engineer, data analysis) is still a viable career in the next 5 years, but the job will look very different than it does today.
AI tools will automate many of the routine tasks :
querying data cleaning data simple exploratory analysis This will free up data analysts to focus on more creative and complex tasks, such as :
interpreting results recommending actions for the business As AI tools become more sophisticated, data analysts who have a deep understanding of a particular domain will be able to create more value for their organizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Continuous Improvement System</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/creating-a-continuous-improvement-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:40:20 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/creating-a-continuous-improvement-system/</guid>
      <description>When we want to accomplish something or achieve a goal, sometimes we succeed, and sometimes we face challenges. Can we find a method that makes it easier to succeed? My answer is PDCA(plan–do–check–adjust). Just do it, let it fail if necessary, and then find a new way to fix it.
What is a system The goal of all science, is to substitute visible complexity for invisible simplicity.
John Baptiste Perrin a system contains 5 part :</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Integration : it&#39;s all about the adapter</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/application-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:53:43 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/application-integration/</guid>
      <description>Integration development is not a standardized term, so there isn&amp;rsquo;t a dedicated page for it on Wikipedia.
In this article, it defines application integration as the process of enabling individual applications to communicate with each other.
For me, integration means adapter. Let me explain it.
Basic skills Fundamental skills :
Protocols : HTTP, XML, messaging protocols, web services, and web sockets are some of the most common protocols used in application integration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six Actionable Steps for Finding a Job</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/six-actionable-steps-for-finding-a-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:26:40 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/six-actionable-steps-for-finding-a-job/</guid>
      <description>Let me introduce six actionable steps for finding a job.
1. get your head right You have to believe that you&amp;rsquo;re going to get a job. Your job is to control what you can control and to shrink the time between now and when you land a job.
2. just do it if you&amp;rsquo;re serious about getting a new job, don&amp;rsquo;t wait to get started. The alternative is wasting years of your life at lower pay with less status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Set Up Google Analytics a Step by Step Guide to Getting Your Measurement Id</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-set-up-google-analytics-a-step-by-step-guide-to-getting-your-measurement-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:03 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-set-up-google-analytics-a-step-by-step-guide-to-getting-your-measurement-id/</guid>
      <description>We use Google Analytics to track the number of visitors to our website, including information about when they visit and how they interact with our site. This helps us understand our audience better and improve our online presence.
when you have a website and want your software engineer to support it with Google Analytics, You need to do two things:
Create a New Property Get the Measurement ID and Send It to Your Software Engineer here is a step-by-step guide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Move Your GoDaddy Domain to Cloudflare a Step by Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-move-your-godaddy-domain-to-cloudflare-a-step-by-step-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:00:29 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-move-your-godaddy-domain-to-cloudflare-a-step-by-step-guide/</guid>
      <description>Managing your domain through Cloudflare offers numerous benefits, including enhanced security, improved website performance, and easy DNS management. These are not the most important factors. The main reason is that you might need my help with day-to-day management, and personally, I prefer Cloudflare.
If you have a domain registered with GoDaddy and want to move it to Cloudflare, follow this detailed step-by-step guide.
Step 1: Create a Cloudflare Account and Add Your Site Create a Cloudflare Account Visit the Cloudflare website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Features in Resume Manager 2</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-features-in-resume-manager-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:46:24 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-features-in-resume-manager-2/</guid>
      <description>Hello, all my friends. Thank you for all your ideas and feedback, help this product better.
We&amp;rsquo;re back! The last update was 18 days ago. This week I use 6 hours to add new feature : Job Application Task Manager. Click here to experience it now.
Here are some of the main interfaces :
New Dashboard Because we added the job application manager, the dashboard has changed.
Job Application List We can add new job applications and change the application status on this page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A First Look At Resume Manager</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/a-first-look-at-resume-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:49:42 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/a-first-look-at-resume-manager/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my friends. Last week, I published a new product: Resume Manager. I have two reasons for creating this product:
to manage my resume and application process, to create a platform for new AI Currently, it is still a demo version, but if you want to try it, you can get started now.
STEP BY STEP visit Resume Manager, click &amp;lsquo;Get Started -&amp;gt;&amp;rsquo; login create new resume change theme Click &amp;lsquo;Next&amp;rsquo; to sequentially edit Personal Detail, Summary, Professional Experience, Education, and Skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating Custom Code Snippets in Vscode</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/creating-custom-code-snippets-in-vscode/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:49:42 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/creating-custom-code-snippets-in-vscode/</guid>
      <description>VSCode provides a powerful snippet feature that helps developers boost their coding efficiency and consistency. This blog will guide you through creating custom code snippets in VSCode, specifically for TypeScript and React projects.
What are Code Snippets? Code snippets are predefined chunks of code that you can quickly insert into your code files using simple shortcuts. They are extremely useful for repetitive tasks or commonly used code templates.
Steps to Manually Create Custom Code Snippets Open VSCode Settings First, open VSCode and press Cmd + Shift + P (Mac) or Ctrl + Shift + P (Windows/Linux) to open the command palette.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minified React Error #130</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/minified-react-error-%23130/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 15:57:51 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/minified-react-error-%23130/</guid>
      <description>When I am unable to find an answer using ChatGPT, Gemini, claude, or Google, I believe it is necessary to document the steps I take to solve the problem.
The problem is :
Unexpected Application Error! Minified React error #130; visit https://reactjs.org/docs/error-decoder.html?invariant=130&amp;amp;args[]=undefined&amp;amp;args[]= for the full message or use the non-minified dev environment for full errors and additional helpful warnings. Error: Minified React error #130; visit https://reactjs.org/docs/error-decoder.html?invariant=130&amp;amp;args[]=undefined&amp;amp;args[]= for the full message or use the non-minified dev environment for full errors and additional helpful warnings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting a blog accepted by Google AdSense</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/getting-a-blog-accepted-by-google-adsense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 10:14:57 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/getting-a-blog-accepted-by-google-adsense/</guid>
      <description>When I first tried to sign up for Google AdSense, I got turned down. Here are the reasons why(the reasons Google gave for turning me down) :
We do not allow Google-served ads on screens: without content or with low value content, that are under construction, that are used for alerts, navigation or other behavioural purposes. So Getting a blog accepted by Google AdSense means you need to creating high quality sites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Yolo to Analyze Youth Football Matches</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/use-yolo-to-analyze-youth-football-matches/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:52:22 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/use-yolo-to-analyze-youth-football-matches/</guid>
      <description>I discuss youth soccer games with my 10-year-old son. I think it&amp;rsquo;s important to first help him understand when making certain decisions is beneficial. So, I&amp;rsquo;m looking for a way to help young athletes develop their decision-making skills.
One important tool for this is watching game videos.
While watching and learning from game videos together, I started thinking about some questions:
Is there a connection between teams that run more and winning?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oduio Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/oduio-roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:37:16 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/oduio-roadmap/</guid>
      <description>last updated on : 2024-07-03
This page displays basic information about the Oduio app,
Oduio means: oh, yes, oh. &amp;lsquo;o&amp;rsquo; stands for &amp;lsquo;oh,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;dui&amp;rsquo; means &amp;lsquo;yes&amp;rsquo; in Chinese pinyin, and &amp;lsquo;o&amp;rsquo; stands for &amp;lsquo;oh.&amp;rsquo;
It is used to express the feeling of a sudden realization. In chinese we say : &amp;lsquo;恍然大悟&amp;rsquo;.
Now Now means plans in progress. Current list :
update news template UI Set the homepage as the LandingPage introduction page, and change the admin dashboard homepage to &amp;lsquo;/home&amp;rsquo; waiting to be scheduled TODO task management module; includes Goal attribute support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 10:57:29 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy
Introduction
Welcome to Shan&amp;rsquo;s Blog. Your privacy is critically important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit our Blog, as well as your rights under GDPR, CPRA, CCPA, CPA, and VCDPA. Please read this policy carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.
Information We Collect
We collect information about you in a variety of ways:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a blog using Hugo</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/create-a-blog-using-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:57:29 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/create-a-blog-using-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Just like you see, this blog you are visiting is created using Hugo and hosted on GitHub Pages. In the process of using Hugo, I researched a lot to answer my questions. Here are some common issues.
How to Create Pages and Posts with Hugo Commands To create a new post in Hugo, you can use the following command:
hugo new posts/your-post-title.md For example, if you want to create a new post titled &amp;ldquo;my-first-post,&amp;rdquo; you would run:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
