<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ResumeManager on shan&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/tags/resumemanager/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ResumeManager on shan&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.128.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:40:20 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://moloxiao.github.io/tags/resumemanager/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Continuous Improvement System</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/creating-a-continuous-improvement-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:40:20 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/creating-a-continuous-improvement-system/</guid>
      <description>When we want to accomplish something or achieve a goal, sometimes we succeed, and sometimes we face challenges. Can we find a method that makes it easier to succeed? My answer is PDCA(plan–do–check–adjust). Just do it, let it fail if necessary, and then find a new way to fix it.
What is a system The goal of all science, is to substitute visible complexity for invisible simplicity. - John Baptiste Perrin a system contains 5 part :</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six Actionable Steps for Finding a Job</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/six-actionable-steps-for-finding-a-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:26:40 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/six-actionable-steps-for-finding-a-job/</guid>
      <description>Let me introduce six actionable steps for finding a job.
1. get your head right You have to believe that you&amp;rsquo;re going to get a job. Your job is to control what you can control and to shrink the time between now and when you land a job.
2. just do it if you&amp;rsquo;re serious about getting a new job, don&amp;rsquo;t wait to get started. The alternative is wasting years of your life at lower pay with less status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Features in Resume Manager 2</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-features-in-resume-manager-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:46:24 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-features-in-resume-manager-2/</guid>
      <description>Hello, all my friends. Thank you for all your ideas and feedback, help this product better.
We&amp;rsquo;re back! The last update was 18 days ago. This week I use 6 hours to add new feature : Job Application Task Manager. Click here to experience it now.
Here are some of the main interfaces :
New Dashboard Because we added the job application manager, the dashboard has changed.
Job Application List We can add new job applications and change the application status on this page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A First Look At Resume Manager</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/a-first-look-at-resume-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:49:42 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/a-first-look-at-resume-manager/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my friends. Last week, I published a new product: Resume Manager. I have two reasons for creating this product:
to manage my resume and application process, to create a platform for new AI Currently, it is still a demo version, but if you want to try it, you can get started now.
STEP BY STEP visit Resume Manager, click &amp;lsquo;Get Started -&amp;gt;&amp;rsquo; login create new resume change theme Click &amp;lsquo;Next&amp;rsquo; to sequentially edit Personal Detail, Summary, Professional Experience, Education, and Skills.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
