<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Job on Shan&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/tags/job/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Job on Shan&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.128.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 20:45:47 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://moloxiao.github.io/tags/job/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare for a Data Jobs</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-prepare-for-a-data-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 20:45:47 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-prepare-for-a-data-jobs/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for data jobs means writing a good resume and passing the job interview.
I want to take immediate action, so I&amp;rsquo;ve set the following principles:
Time allocation principle: Focus on securing interview opportunities before receiving any interviews; once an interview is secured, focus on interview preparation. Take action first, then reflect and improve as you go. Therefore, we start with the resume, which includes two important factors:
A well-formatted resume.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Jobs in 2024</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/data-jobs-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 11:43:19 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/data-jobs-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>1 About Data Jobs Data Jobs(like data engineer, data analysis) is still a viable career in the next 5 years, but the job will look very different than it does today.
AI tools will automate many of the routine tasks :
querying data cleaning data simple exploratory analysis This will free up data analysts to focus on more creative and complex tasks, such as :
interpreting results recommending actions for the business As AI tools become more sophisticated, data analysts who have a deep understanding of a particular domain will be able to create more value for their organizations.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
