<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Shan&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Shan&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.128.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 14:53:00 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Daily Brainstorming : How to Evaluate Whether a New Project Is Good</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/daily-brainstorming-how-to-evaluate-whether-a-new-project-is-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 14:53:00 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/daily-brainstorming-how-to-evaluate-whether-a-new-project-is-good/</guid>
      <description>In this blog, I share insights as a software engineer on the challenge of assessing new projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year Holiday Reading Book 3 How to Raise a Tech Genius</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-year-holiday-reading-book-3-how-to-raise-a-tech-genius/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 16:15:31 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-year-holiday-reading-book-3-how-to-raise-a-tech-genius/</guid>
      <description>How to Raise a Tech Genius : Develop your child&amp;#39;s computing skills without spending any money</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year Holiday Reading Book 2 Design and Build Great Web Apis</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-year-holiday-reading-book-2-design-and-build-great-web-apis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 11:01:04 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-year-holiday-reading-book-2-design-and-build-great-web-apis/</guid>
      <description>.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year Holiday Reading Book 1 : Business Intelligence Analytics Data Science and Ai</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-year-holiday-reading-book-1-business-intelligence-analytics-data-science-and-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 20:36:02 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-year-holiday-reading-book-1-business-intelligence-analytics-data-science-and-ai/</guid>
      <description>This is a comprehensive book (Business Intelligence Analytics and Data Science : A Managerial Perspective), perfect for browsing through.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Do Not Need Learn Everything in the Code</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/you-do-not-need-learn-everything-in-the-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 10:40:54 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/you-do-not-need-learn-everything-in-the-code/</guid>
      <description>You Do Not Need Learn Everything in the Code. Which is impossible. Pick a tech stack and learn as much as you can about that group of technologies. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fix Replicate Run Error Readablestream in Nextjs</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-fix-replicate-run-error-readablestream-in-nextjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:53:31 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-fix-replicate-run-error-readablestream-in-nextjs/</guid>
      <description>Fix the error when using the Replicate Node.js client in a Next.js application to retrieve the URL response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can We Make a Simple Software</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/can-we-make-a-simple-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 15:25:30 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/can-we-make-a-simple-software/</guid>
      <description>Can We Make a Simple Software or Why Can&amp;#39;t We Make Simple Software? Let&amp;#39;s talk about it from Complexity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello Accounting</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/hello-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 16:40:33 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/hello-accounting/</guid>
      <description>My Notes on Accounting, Driven by Personal Interest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best Places for Camping in Invercargill</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/the-best-places-for-camping-in-invercargill/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 22:11:45 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/the-best-places-for-camping-in-invercargill/</guid>
      <description>The Best Places for Camping in Invercargill</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading Notes Series 1 Achieving Rapid Response Times</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/reading-notes-series-1-achieving-rapid-response-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 15:30:57 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/reading-notes-series-1-achieving-rapid-response-times/</guid>
      <description>Notes and key insights from the paper &amp;#39;Achieving Rapid Response Times in Large Online Services&amp;#39; by Jeff Dean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Prepared for the PTE Test</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-i-prepared-for-the-pte-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 15:10:00 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-i-prepared-for-the-pte-test/</guid>
      <description>A personal guide to preparing for the PTE Test in 2024, with strategies and lessons learned along the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build Confidence in Your Kids</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-build-confidence-in-your-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 22:05:28 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-build-confidence-in-your-kids/</guid>
      <description>One day, our children will leave us to live independently, and the role of parents will also change. When they move forward on their own, I hope they are filled with confidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shan Side Project Monthly Update 01 October 2024</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/shan-side-project-monthly-update-01-october-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 17:12:19 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/shan-side-project-monthly-update-01-october-2024/</guid>
      <description>Shan Side Project Monthly Update 01 October 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding It Consultant Levels</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/understanding-it-consultant-levels/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:04:36 +1300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/understanding-it-consultant-levels/</guid>
      <description>Understanding IT Consultant Levels: A Breakdown with AWS, Microsoft, and Google Certifications</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Write Code Using AI Assistance</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-write-code-using-ai-assistance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 10:53:23 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-write-code-using-ai-assistance/</guid>
      <description>how to write code Using AI-assistance By Andrew Ng. This is Shan&amp;#39;s notes. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essential Tools and Tips for Daily Church Website Management</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/essential-tools-and-tips-for-daily-church-website-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:11:01 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/essential-tools-and-tips-for-daily-church-website-management/</guid>
      <description>Toolset for Daily Management of CornerstoneCongregational.org</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relational Databases and Normalization</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/relational-databases-and-normalization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:01:22 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/relational-databases-and-normalization/</guid>
      <description>Normalization forms the foundation of relational databases. In this article, we walk through an example, applying 1NF, 2NF, and 3NF step by step, illustrating how normalization guides the design of a well-structured relational table.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Summary Framework for Resume Submissions</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/weekly-summary-framework-for-resume-submissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 21:30:07 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/weekly-summary-framework-for-resume-submissions/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes it takes a long time to find a job, and you might feel discouraged, but the most important thing is to keep going. A weekly summary can help you stay on track and not give up. This is the method I used.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customize Your Resume According to the Job Description</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/customize-your-resume-according-to-the-job-description/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 09:14:29 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/customize-your-resume-according-to-the-job-description/</guid>
      <description>In the current Resume Manager application, the module I use the most on a daily basis is the job application module, with its core feature being the tracking of resume submissions. Moving forward, I want to enhance the ability to match resumes with job requirements. This will involve the following steps:
Analysis of the recruitment process and the needs of each stage Resume Match evaluation Process adjustment 1 Analysis of the recruitment process and the needs of each stage Stage Goal Evaluation Criteria Resume Screening Initial screening to find candidates that meet basic job requirements Core skills Years of experience Education requirements Career objectives and cultural fit Initial/Phone Interview Further assess communication skills, motivation, and cultural fit Communication skills Career motivation Problem-solving ability Cultural fit Technical Assessment Evaluate candidates&amp;rsquo; technical proficiency and problem-solving skills Technical skills Problem-solving ability Project experience and technical expertise Behavioral/Deep Interview Assess leadership, teamwork, and deeper cultural fit Leadership Teamwork Cultural fit Handling challenges Final Interview/Decision Ensure long-term potential within the company and alignment of compensation expectations Overall competence Role expectations and company growth alignment Salary negotiation and benefits expectations 2 Resume Match evaluation the three most important aspects of a resume are :</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create an Industrial Automation Solutions Website</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/create-an-industrial-automation-solutions-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:43:08 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/create-an-industrial-automation-solutions-website/</guid>
      <description>I want to consolidate my experience and knowledge in the field of automation, and I’ve decided to do this by creating a website. I also hope it can serve as a starting point for offering consulting services.
Since this website is content-focused, I chose to build it using Docusaurus and deployed it on Cloudflare. I spent an hour setting up the template and configuring automated deployment. You can now access it by clicking here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Method for Quickly Mastering the USNR Scanning System</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/a-method-for-quickly-mastering-the-usnr-scanning-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 22:17:29 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/a-method-for-quickly-mastering-the-usnr-scanning-system/</guid>
      <description>I have never used the USNR Scanning system before. This article outlines my plan for quickly mastering the system and developing the capability for ongoing maintenance and improvement.
1 Goals &amp;amp; Metrics The goal can be divided into two stages :
Proficiency : Become familiar with the USNR system as an assistant, understand the manual, learn the operating procedures, and handle common issues. Control : Understand the wood processing steps, and master the role of the USNR system at each step Tasks for Proficiency :</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare for Data Jobs</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-prepare-for-data-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 20:45:47 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-prepare-for-data-jobs/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for data jobs means writing a good resume and passing the job interview.
I want to take immediate action, so I&amp;rsquo;ve set the following principles:
Time allocation principle: Focus on securing interview opportunities before receiving any interviews; once an interview is secured, focus on interview preparation. Take action first, then reflect and improve as you go. Therefore, we start with the resume, which includes two important factors:
A well-formatted resume.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Jobs in 2024</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/data-jobs-in-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 11:43:19 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/data-jobs-in-2024/</guid>
      <description>1 About Data Jobs Data Jobs(like data engineer, data analysis) is still a viable career in the next 5 years, but the job will look very different than it does today.
AI tools will automate many of the routine tasks :
querying data cleaning data simple exploratory analysis This will free up data analysts to focus on more creative and complex tasks, such as :
interpreting results recommending actions for the business As AI tools become more sophisticated, data analysts who have a deep understanding of a particular domain will be able to create more value for their organizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Continuous Improvement System</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/creating-a-continuous-improvement-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:40:20 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/creating-a-continuous-improvement-system/</guid>
      <description>When we want to accomplish something or achieve a goal, sometimes we succeed, and sometimes we face challenges. Can we find a method that makes it easier to succeed? My answer is PDCA(plan–do–check–adjust). Just do it, let it fail if necessary, and then find a new way to fix it.
What is a system The goal of all science, is to substitute visible complexity for invisible simplicity.
John Baptiste Perrin a system contains 5 part :</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Integration : it&#39;s all about the adapter</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/application-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:53:43 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/application-integration/</guid>
      <description>Integration development is not a standardized term, so there isn&amp;rsquo;t a dedicated page for it on Wikipedia.
In this article, it defines application integration as the process of enabling individual applications to communicate with each other.
For me, integration means adapter. Let me explain it.
Basic skills Fundamental skills :
Protocols : HTTP, XML, messaging protocols, web services, and web sockets are some of the most common protocols used in application integration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six Actionable Steps for Finding a Job</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/six-actionable-steps-for-finding-a-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:26:40 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/six-actionable-steps-for-finding-a-job/</guid>
      <description>Let me introduce six actionable steps for finding a job.
1. get your head right You have to believe that you&amp;rsquo;re going to get a job. Your job is to control what you can control and to shrink the time between now and when you land a job.
2. just do it if you&amp;rsquo;re serious about getting a new job, don&amp;rsquo;t wait to get started. The alternative is wasting years of your life at lower pay with less status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Set Up Google Analytics a Step by Step Guide to Getting Your Measurement Id</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-set-up-google-analytics-a-step-by-step-guide-to-getting-your-measurement-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:29:03 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-set-up-google-analytics-a-step-by-step-guide-to-getting-your-measurement-id/</guid>
      <description>We use Google Analytics to track the number of visitors to our website, including information about when they visit and how they interact with our site. This helps us understand our audience better and improve our online presence.
when you have a website and want your software engineer to support it with Google Analytics, You need to do two things:
Create a New Property Get the Measurement ID and Send It to Your Software Engineer here is a step-by-step guide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Move Your GoDaddy Domain to Cloudflare a Step by Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-move-your-godaddy-domain-to-cloudflare-a-step-by-step-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:00:29 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/how-to-move-your-godaddy-domain-to-cloudflare-a-step-by-step-guide/</guid>
      <description>Managing your domain through Cloudflare offers numerous benefits, including enhanced security, improved website performance, and easy DNS management. These are not the most important factors. The main reason is that you might need my help with day-to-day management, and personally, I prefer Cloudflare.
If you have a domain registered with GoDaddy and want to move it to Cloudflare, follow this detailed step-by-step guide.
Step 1: Create a Cloudflare Account and Add Your Site Create a Cloudflare Account Visit the Cloudflare website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Features in Resume Manager 2</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-features-in-resume-manager-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:46:24 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/new-features-in-resume-manager-2/</guid>
      <description>Hello, all my friends. Thank you for all your ideas and feedback, help this product better.
We&amp;rsquo;re back! The last update was 18 days ago. This week I use 6 hours to add new feature : Job Application Task Manager. Click here to experience it now.
Here are some of the main interfaces :
New Dashboard Because we added the job application manager, the dashboard has changed.
Job Application List We can add new job applications and change the application status on this page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shan&#39;s Responses to Common Interview Questions</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/shan-responses-to-common-interview-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:36:34 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/shan-responses-to-common-interview-questions/</guid>
      <description>Shan&amp;#39;s suggest Responses to Common Interview Questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A First Look At Resume Manager</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/a-first-look-at-resume-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:49:42 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/a-first-look-at-resume-manager/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my friends. Last week, I published a new product: Resume Manager. I have two reasons for creating this product:
to manage my resume and application process, to create a platform for new AI Currently, it is still a demo version, but if you want to try it, you can get started now.
STEP BY STEP visit Resume Manager, click &amp;lsquo;Get Started -&amp;gt;&amp;rsquo; login create new resume change theme Click &amp;lsquo;Next&amp;rsquo; to sequentially edit Personal Detail, Summary, Professional Experience, Education, and Skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating Custom Code Snippets in Vscode</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/creating-custom-code-snippets-in-vscode/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:49:42 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/creating-custom-code-snippets-in-vscode/</guid>
      <description>VSCode provides a powerful snippet feature that helps developers boost their coding efficiency and consistency. This blog will guide you through creating custom code snippets in VSCode, specifically for TypeScript and React projects.
What are Code Snippets? Code snippets are predefined chunks of code that you can quickly insert into your code files using simple shortcuts. They are extremely useful for repetitive tasks or commonly used code templates.
Steps to Manually Create Custom Code Snippets Open VSCode Settings First, open VSCode and press Cmd + Shift + P (Mac) or Ctrl + Shift + P (Windows/Linux) to open the command palette.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minified React Error #130</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/minified-react-error-%23130/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 15:57:51 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/minified-react-error-%23130/</guid>
      <description>how to fix Minified React error #130</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting a blog accepted by Google AdSense</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/getting-a-blog-accepted-by-google-adsense/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 10:14:57 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/getting-a-blog-accepted-by-google-adsense/</guid>
      <description>Getting a blog accepted by Google AdSense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Yolo to Analyze Youth Football Matches</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/use-yolo-to-analyze-youth-football-matches/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:52:22 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/use-yolo-to-analyze-youth-football-matches/</guid>
      <description>I discuss youth soccer games with my 10-year-old son. I think it&amp;rsquo;s important to first help him understand when making certain decisions is beneficial. So, I&amp;rsquo;m looking for a way to help young athletes develop their decision-making skills.
One important tool for this is watching game videos.
While watching and learning from game videos together, I started thinking about some questions:
Is there a connection between teams that run more and winning?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oduio Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/oduio-roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:37:16 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/oduio-roadmap/</guid>
      <description>last updated on : 2024-07-03
This page displays basic information about the Oduio app,
Oduio means: oh, yes, oh. &amp;lsquo;o&amp;rsquo; stands for &amp;lsquo;oh,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;dui&amp;rsquo; means &amp;lsquo;yes&amp;rsquo; in Chinese pinyin, and &amp;lsquo;o&amp;rsquo; stands for &amp;lsquo;oh.&amp;rsquo;
It is used to express the feeling of a sudden realization. In chinese we say : &amp;lsquo;恍然大悟&amp;rsquo;.
Now Now means plans in progress. Current list :
update news template UI Set the homepage as the LandingPage introduction page, and change the admin dashboard homepage to &amp;lsquo;/home&amp;rsquo; waiting to be scheduled TODO task management module; includes Goal attribute support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a blog using Hugo</title>
      <link>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/create-a-blog-using-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 20:57:29 +1200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moloxiao.github.io/posts/create-a-blog-using-hugo/</guid>
      <description>How I created my blog using Hugo and the tools I used.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
